# JUAN C. BARRIOS S.

# SENIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER

# SKILLS PROFESSIONALS

JavaScript
TypeScript
React
Next
Node
Flutter
React Native

# SKILLS PERSONALS

Creative
Trustworthy and professional
Organized
Time management
Teamwork
Fast learner
Motivated

#### CONTACT

+58 4121556808 juanbarrios045@gmail.com https://juanbs.com/

## REFERENCES

#### JUNIOR SÁNCHEZ

Developer FullStack jysa65.dev@gmail.com

#### MOISÉS DE LA CRUZ

Backend Developer and DevOps moiseslacruz16@gmail.com

## **LENNON PEREZ**

Front End Developer lenonart14@gmail.com

#### **PROFILE**

My name is Juan, I'm 23 years old and I'm from Venezuela. I am a big fan of web development and technology. I am passionate about working as a front end developer and I always make sure that what I develop is perfect. I am great at working in a team and I adjust to everything you need.

I'm a Senior Front End Developer with more than five year of work experience.



# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **MONOMA**

March 2024 - July 2024

#### **ASP CONSULTING**

May 2023 - March 2024

#### **TAUROS**

Nov 2019 - Feb 2023

#### **FREELANCER**

Sep 2019 - Present

#### **EDUCATION**

#### SYSTEMS ANALYST

Instituto Universitario de Tecnología para la informatica | 2017 - 2020